A Guide to the Papers of Irby B. Cauthen, 1940-1968
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Irby B. Cauthen 1940-1968
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
12769-c
This collection consists of 300 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift of Irby B. Cauthen on 1987 September 7.
Contents List
- English courses taken by Cauthen at the University of Virginia.
  - Bibliography 1949 (Box 1)
  - Eighteenth Century Notes 1940's (Box 1)
  - Elizabethan Non-Dramatic Literature (1 of 2) 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - Elizabethan Non-Dramatic Literature (2 of 2) 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - Novel-English C1 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - Romantic Literature 1947-1956 (Box 1)
  - Seventeenth Century Notes 1942 (Box 1)
  - Shakespeare Notes N.D. (Box 1)
  - Shakespeare Papers 1948-1951 (Box 1)
  - Spenser Course-Fredson Bowers-Paper 1950 (Box 1)
  - Victorian Literature 1949 (Box 1)
- Bread Loaf Courses
  - Bread Loaf-American Folk Literature-Donald Davidson 1947 (Box 2)
  - Bread Loaf-Modern Poetry-Elizabeth Drew 1947 (Box 2)
- Courses Cauthen taught at the University of Virginia.
  - Criticism 1955-1956 (Box 2)
  - Eighteenth Century-English 26 1956-1957 (Box 2)
  - Elizabethan-English 25 1954-1956 (Box 2)
  - Pre-Renaissance-English 25 1955-1956 (Box 2)
  - Shakespeare Exam-English 14 1968 (Box 2)
  - Shakespeare Tests 1950-1951 (Box 2)
  - Extension Division-Baroque 1954-1957 (Box 2)
- English Departmental Matters
  - English Dept.-Contemporary Literature (handouts) 1950's (Box 2)
  - English Dept.-Exams-Comprehensives (1 of 2) 1953-1968 (Box 2)
  - English Dept.-Exams-Comprehensives (2 of 2) 1953-1968 (Box 2)
  - English Dept.-Faculty-Dept. Matters 1955-1957 (Box 2)